http://www.vcc.ca/about/college-information/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - Vancouver Community College
COVID-19 latest update:
Design
CAD and BIM (Drafting)
Technology
CAD and BIM (Drafting)
Programs
Academic Upgrading – Computers (Self-paced)
Academic Upgrading – English, Social Sciences and Humanities
Academic Upgrading – English, Social Sciences and Humanities (Self-paced)
Academic Upgrading – Mathematics
Academic Upgrading – Mathematics (Self-paced)
Academic Upgrading – Sciences
Academic Upgrading – Sciences (Self-paced)
Adult Basic Education (ABE) Graduation
Adult Basic Education (ABE) Graduation (Self-paced)
Adult Basic Education (ABE) Intermediate
Adult Basic Education (ABE) Intermediate (Self-paced)
Adult Basic Education (ABE) Intermediate – Youth
Architectural Technician (Certificate)
Bachelor of Hospitality Management
Bachelor of Hospitality Management (Executive Cohort)
Business Leadership and Management
CAD and BIM Architectural Technician (Diploma)
CAD and BIM Civil/Structural Technician (Diploma)
CAD Technician (Certificate)
Career Access
Career Awareness
Civil/Structural Technician (Certificate)
Dental Assisting – Certified
Dental Assisting – Certified (Online)
Diesel Engine Mechanic Apprentice
Early Childhood Care and Education (Certificate)
Early Childhood Care and Education (Diploma)
Early Childhood Education Post-Basic (Infant Toddler and Special Needs)
Executive Assistant
Fashion Design & Production (Certificate)
Fashion Design & Production (Diploma)
Gladue Report Writing
Graphic Design (Diploma)
Heavy Mechanical Trades Foundation
Hospitality Management (Diploma)
IT Operations Professional (Certificate)
IT Operations Professional (Short Certificate)
Jewellery Art and Design
Leadership
Leadership Coaching (Associate Certificate)
Leadership Coaching (Certificate)
Medical Transcriptionist
Music (Diploma)
Network Security Advanced Certificate
Networking Technology
Nursing (BScN)
Nursing (BScN) (Advanced Entry)
Occupational/Physical Therapist Assistant (Rehab Assistant)
Online/eLearning Instruction
Paralegal (Certificate)
Paralegal (Diploma)
Professional Cook 2
Provincial Instructor Diploma Program (PIDP)
Records Management Skills
Renal Dialysis Technician
Retail and Hospitality Careers
Rick Hansen Foundation Accessibility Certification™ (RHFAC) Training
Samsung Tech Institute - Appliance Repair Technician
Sport and Recreation Management
Steel Construction Modelling Technician (Certificate)
Teaching English to Speakers of Other Languages (TESOL) (Certificate)
Teaching English to Speakers of Other Languages (TESOL) (Diploma)
Truck and Transport Mechanic Apprentice
University Transfer (Courses)
University Transfer – Applied Mathematics (SFU)
University Transfer – Applied Physics (SFU)
University Transfer – Arts
University Transfer – Biological Physics (SFU)
University Transfer – Biological Sciences (SFU)
University Transfer – Chemistry (SFU)
University Transfer – Computing Science and Software Systems
University Transfer – Engineering (SFU)
University Transfer – Engineering (UBC)
University Transfer – Environmental Studies
University Transfer – Mathematics (SFU)
University Transfer – Molecular Biology and Biochemistry (SFU)
University Transfer – Pathway to Health Sciences
University Transfer – Physics (SFU)
University Transfer – Science
University Transfer – Science (UBC)
University Transfer – Software Systems (SFU)
University Transfer – Statistics (SFU)
Study at VCC
Academic UpgradingApprenticeship TrainingBaking and CulinaryBusinessDesignEnglish as a Second LanguageHair, Esthetics and MakeupHealth SciencesHospitalityHuman and Family ServicesInstructor TrainingLanguages and WritingMusic and DanceStudents with DisabilitiesTechnologyTransportation TradesUniversity TransferYouth Train in Trades
Search Programs
Search Courses
Part-time
Full-time
Programs A-Z
Continuing Studies
Indigenous Learners
International Students
Apply Now
Admissions, Registration and RecordsAdvising ServicesAssessmentsEnglish Language Proficiency RequirementsFees and PaymentsFinancial Aid
Indigenous LearnersApprenticeshipStudents with DisabilitiesInternational Students
Services for Students
Current Students
Eat, Shop + More
Advising ServicesBookstoreCareer GuidanceChild CareCounsellingDisability ServicesDispute ResolutionIndigenous ServicesInterpreting ServicesLibraryTutoring
Admissions and Student RecordsApplication for GraduationAwardsConvocationImportant DatesmyVCC and Tax FormsRegister for CoursesSecurity & Risk ManagementStudents' Union - SUVCCU-Pass & Compass CardWi-Fi
Asian culinary arts Auto ShopBlenzCafeteriaDental ClinicGift CardsJJ's RestaurantSeiffert MarketSpace rentals and filmingThe BistroThe Chef’s Table pop-up kitchenVCC Salon & Spa
College Information
Governance & Policies
News / Events
About VCCCampus Master PlanCareersCommunity ReportContact UsIntegrated College PlanMediaReports and Publications
Board of GovernorsAbout the PresidentEducation CouncilPoliciesProcurementQuality AssuranceInclement Weather
News
Events
Important Dates
Contact Us
Work at VCC
Support
Social Media
Ask an Advisor
Student Recruiters
VCC Foundation & Alumni
Addresses
Employee Directory
Services Directory
Career OpportunitiesWorking at VCCExcellence AwardsContact HR
Partnership Development OfficeResearch at VCCVCC Foundation & AlumniWays to GiveSign Up for NewsAlumni Deals and PerksOutstanding Alumni Awards
Facebook
Twitter
Instagram
YouTube
Flickr
RSS
More accounts
Home
AboutCollege InformationPrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Vancouver Community College is committed to protecting your privacy. You can visit most pages on our site without giving us any information about yourself. But sometimes we do need information to provide services that you request, and this privacy statement explains data collection and use in those situations.
Information we collect When you register at any of Vancouver Community College's websites, we may ask to collect personal details, such as your name, postal address and email address. For further information about how we use your personal information, see our registration statement.
We also collect Website usage information and information about your Web browser and Internet connection, including your computer's IP address, the type and version of browser and operating system you use and, if you arrived at the site via a link from another Website, the URL of the linking page. For further information about how we use this usage information, see our website usage statement.
Cookies A cookie is a small piece of information, stored on your computer during a visit to Vancouver Community College's websites. This information allows you to move quickly and easily around our sites. For further information, see our cookie statement.
External Links Vancouver Community College's websites contain links to websites not owned or operated by Vancouver Community College. Vancouver Community College is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We recommend that you read the privacy statement of each such Website to find out how they protect your personal information.
For Your Security Always remember to log off or log out after you have completed your online session. If you suspect any unusual activity, please contact us immediately.
Use Of Our Website By using our Website, you consent to the collection and use of information by Vancouver Community College as specified above. If we decide to change our privacy statement, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
If you have any queries regarding Vancouver Community College's online privacy statement or the use of your information, please contact us.
Follow Us:
Subscribe to VCC's monthly newsletter for news about college events, information sessions, registrations dates, contests and more.
